Guide to the Gitel P. Steed Papers 1907-1980
University of Chicago Library
- Series VIII: Manuscripts and Publications by Others
  - Ray, Verne F., editor, Systems of Political Control and Bureaucracy in Human Societies, proceedings of the American Ethnological Society meetings, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Redfield, Robert, and Milton Singer, "The Cultural Role of Cities," 1954 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Rosenfeld, Gerard L., "Anthropology as Social Studies in the Elementary School," "Cultural Influences Shaping the Role of the Child," 1965 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Rowe, William L., "The Meaning of Urban Migration for North Indian Villagers," 1960 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Sen Gupta, Bhabani, "A Maoist Line for India," 1967 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Shue, Vivienne, "Radical Redistribution with Mass Mobilization: Roots of Rural Development in China," 1975 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Silverberg, James, "Class Conflict in a Caste-Structured System," 1958, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Singh, Harbans, "Social Change and Social Mobilization in Contemporary Indian Cities," manuscript fragment, undated (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Singh, Rudra Datt, "The Unity of an Indian Village," 1956 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Slater, Marian, "Let Them Eat S----," undated (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - "The Social Novel," in Hindi, Bengali, and Urdu, abstracts, undated (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Social Science Research Council, Conference on Economic Growth in Seclected Countries, manuscripts on India, 1952 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Sopa, Geshe, "The Two Leading Principles of Buddhist Meditation," undated (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Southern Asian Institute, Seminar on Tradition and Change in South and Southeast Asia, correspondence, memoranda, reprints, 1969-1974 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Stiles, George, "General Bullet," short story, undated (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Studies in social change, abstracts, undated (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Suffian, Tun Mohamed, "The Influence of the American Constitution on the Malaysian Constitution," 1976 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Suri, Surinder, "Modernization: A Myth," 1970 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Tangri, Shanti S., "Urban Growth, City Size, and Social Overhead Capital: The Case of India," 1972 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Thelen, Herbert A., and Jacob W. Getzels, "The Social Sciences: Conceptual Framework for Education," undated (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Thomas, Emmanuel, "Some Dimensions of Urbanization and Their Differential Impact on Modernization in India," 1972 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Tilman, Robert O., "Confucius among the Barbarians," undated (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Towles, Joseph, "Ritual and Structure," undated (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Tripathi, P. K., "Perspectives on the American Constitutional Influence in India," 1976 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Ukai, Nobushige, "The Significance of the Reception of American Constitutional Institutions and Ideas in Japan," 1976 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - UNESCO, Group Tension Research Project in India, statement of objectives, 1950-1951 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Weiner, Myron, "Party Building in a New Nation," chapter manuscript, undated (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Weinreich, Uriel, "The Troubles of Hindi," 1957 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Whyte, William H., Jr., "The Fallacies of `Personality Testing,' magazine clipping, 1954 (Box 82, Folder 26)
- Series IX: Oversize
  - Thematic Apperception Test (TAT), additional cards, undated (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Thematic Apperception Test (TAT), negatives, undated (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Thematic Apperception Test (TAT), cards (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Thematic Apperception Test (TAT), cards (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Thematic Apperception Test (TAT), cards (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Surveyor of India, "Survey of India Map Catalogue," provisional edition (corrected), 1945 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Informant 2, Draw-a-man (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Khata-vati (Village) Settlement Register, complete, handwritten, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Watercolors, Informant 1, self-portraits (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Watercolors, Informant 1, portraits (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Watercolors, Informant 1, landscapes (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Watercolors, Informant 1, house interiors (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Watercolors, Informant 1, village scenes (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Watercolors, Informant 1, mythological themes (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Watercolors, Informant 3 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Watercolors, Informant 16 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Watercolors, drawings, miscellaneous (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Drawings, Informant 1 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Drawings, Informant 3 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Drawings, miscellaneous (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - University of Chicago exhibition notes, undated (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Negatives, contact sheets (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Negatives, contact sheets (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Negatives, contact sheets (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Negatives, contact sheets (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Negatives, contact sheets (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Negatives, contact sheets (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Contact sheets (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Women and children, 12 prints (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Women and children, 12 prints (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Women and children, 12 prints (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Women and children, 12 prints (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Women and children, 12 prints (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Women and children, 12 prints (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Woman, man and child, 2 prints (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Children, 4 prints (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Children, 4 prints (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Children, 14 prints (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Children, 14 prints (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Children, 14 prints (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Children, 14 prints (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Children, 14 prints (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Children, 14 prints (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Women, 4 prints (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Women, 4 prints (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Men, 8 prints (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Men, 8 prints (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Men, 8 prints (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Men, 8 prints (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Painting, 4 prints (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Painting, 4 prints (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Work and material culture, 6 prints (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Work and material culture, 6 prints (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Work and material culture, 6 prints (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Gods and temples, 4 prints (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Gods and temples, 4 prints (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Ritual, 5 prints (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Ritual, 5 prints (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Ritual, Holi, 4 prints (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Ritual, Holi, 4 prints (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - Ritual, wedding, 3 prints (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - Ritual, negatives, contact sheets (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 31)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 32)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 33)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 34)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 35)
  - Gods and temples, watercolors (Box 87, Folder 36)
  - Greenland Inuit, 10 maps, 3 charts, notes, undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Caste, kinship, 35 charts, maps and charts, undated (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Caste, kinship, 35 charts, maps and charts, undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Geopolitical divisions, states, villages, 38 maps, 5 charts, notes, maps and charts, undated (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Geopolitical divisions, states, villages, 38 maps, 5 charts, notes, maps and charts, undated (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - "New India in the Making," review of Development for Free Asia by Maurice Zinkin, Times Literary Supplement, January 25, 1957 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - India, nation and state, eight maps (DRAWER 1, Folder 1)
  - Western India, region and district, ten maps (DRAWER 1, Folder 2)
  - Kasandra, village, sacred geography, landholding, twenty maps, 1950 (DRAWER 1, Folder 3)
  - Kinship and genealogies, eighteen charts, 1950 (DRAWER 1, Folder 4)
  - Caste, territory, demography, nine charts, 1950 (DRAWER 1, Folder 5)
  - Gujarat, district and Taluk, land tenure, demography, twelve maps (DRAWER 2, Folder 1)
  - Kasandra, village, one map, 1950 (DRAWER 2, Folder 2)
  - Watercolors, Informant 1, mythological themes, 2 images (DRAWER 2, Folder 3)
- Series X: Duplicate Files
  These are duplicate files that were removed from this series during the processing of this collection.
  - Informant lists (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Informant 1, personal narration interviews, 1-3 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Informant 1, personal narration interviews, 4-18 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Informant 1, personal narration interviews, 1-10 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Informant 1, tests, draw-a-man, color association (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Informant 2, personal narration [3 duplicates, two complete] (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Informant 2, personal narration [3 duplicates, two complete] (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Informant 2, personal narration [3 duplicates, two complete] (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Informant 2, tests (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Informant 2, Rorschach analysis (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Informant 2, index to sociological documents [2 duplicates] (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Informant 3, personal narration, interviews 6-20 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Informant 3, personal narration, 1-20 [2 duplicates] (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Informant 3, personal narration, 1-20 [2 duplicates] (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Informant 3, tests (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Informant 3, index (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Informant 4, Rorschach (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Informant 4, personal narration (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Informant 5, Rorschach, TAT [2 duplicates]. (2) (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Informant 7, Rorschach [2 duplicates]. (2) (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Informant 10, personal narration (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Informant 10, tests (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Informant 12, Rorschach [2 duplicates]. (2) (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Informant 13, Rorschach (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Informant 14, Rorschach (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - Informant 15, tests (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Informant 18, personal narration (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - Informant 19, Rorschach (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Informant 32, personal narration, interview 2 (Box 91, Folder 29)
  - Informant 33, personal narration (Box 91, Folder 30)
  - Informant 33, Rorschach (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Informant 175, child development test (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Informant 175, Rorschach [2 duplicates]. (2) (Box 91, Folder 32)
  - Psychodiagnostic tests, Rorschachs (Box 91, Folder 33)
  - Psychodiagnostic tests, TATs (Box 92, Folder 34)
  - Psychodiagnostic tests, Horn-Hellersberg (Box 92, Folder 35)
  - Koli, data, James Silverberg notes, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 36-38)
  - Economics, service relations, land tenure, charts (Box 92, Folder 39)
  - Economics, questionnaires (Box 92, Folder 40)
  - Economics, land, survey data (Box 92, Folder 41)
  - Economics, land tenure, village record of rights (Box 92, Folder 42)
  - Land use survey, Book I (Box 92, Folder 43)
  - Land use survey, Book II (Box 92, Folder 44)
  - Land use survey, Book III (Box 92, Folder 45)
  - Land use survey, Books I-III (Box 92, Folder 46)
  - Khata-vati settlement register, 1947 (Box 92, Folder 47)
  - Structure of child behavior, outline (Box 92, Folder 48)
  - Structure of child behavior, Informant 58 (Box 92, Folder 49)
  - Religion, principles, texts, literature (Box 93, Folder 50)
  - Religion, personnel (Box 93, Folder 51)
  - Religion, sorcery, curing practices (Box 93, Folder 52)
  - Lecture 7, November 5, 1952 (Box 93, Folder 53)
  - James Silverberg general notes, February 2-10, 1950 (Box 93, Folder 54)
  - James Silverberg general notes, February 11-16, 1950 (Box 93, Folder 55)
  - James Silverberg general notes, February 17-March 4, 1950 (Box 93, Folder 56)
  - Informant list, watercolors (Box 93, Folder 57)
  - Informant [Allahbux], personal narration (Box 93, Folder 58)
  - General Notes, Gitel P. Steed, outline/index (Box 93, Folder 59)
  - General Notes, Gitel P. Steed, I [2 duplicates] (Box 93, Folder 60)
  - General Notes, Gitel P. Steed, II [2 duplicates] (Box 93, Folder 61)
  - Lecture 7 (Box 93, Folder 62)
  - Lecture (Box 93, Folder 63)
  - Lecture 9 (Box 93, Folder 64)
  - Lecture 9-10 (Box 93, Folder 65)
  - Reading notes, undated (Box 93, Folder 66)
  - Hofstra University, Research in Cross-cultural Studies, Research in Contemporary India Project, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 67)
  - [Adhon] Kinship, census (Box 93, Folder 68)
  - Ratings (Box 93, Folder 69)
  - Land Utilization Survey, form 1 (Box 93, Folder 70)
  - Land Use Survey, ratings, tabulations (Box 93, Folder 71)
  - Religion, Islam (Box 93, Folder 72)
  - Religion, Holi, Phuldo organization (Box 93, Folder 73)
  - John Koos art notes (Box 93, Folder 74)
  - Court cases, crime (Box 93, Folder 75)
  - Jajmani relations (Box 93, Folder 76)
  - Personal narration, Informant 1 [2 copies] (Box 94, Folder 77)
  - Personal narration, Informant 1 [2 copies] (Box 94, Folder 78)
  - Personal narration, Informant 3 [2 copies] (Box 94, Folder 79)
  - Personal narration, Informant 3 [2 copies] (Box 94, Folder 80)
  - Personal narration, Informant 4 [2 copies] (Box 94, Folder 81)
  - Personal narration, Informant 4 [2 copies] (Box 94, Folder 82)
  - Personal narration, Informant 5 [2 copies] (Box 94, Folder 83)
  - Personal narration, Informant 5 [2 copies] (Box 94, Folder 84)
  - Personal narration, Unnumbered informant [2 copies] (Box 94, Folder 85)
  - Personal narration, Unnumbered informant [2 copies] (Box 94, Folder 86)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, January [2 duplicates] (Box 94, Folder 87)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, January [2 duplicates] (Box 94, Folder 88)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, February [2 duplicates] (Box 94, Folder 89)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, February [2 duplicates] (Box 94, Folder 90)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, March [2 duplicates] (Box 94, Folder 91)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, March [2 duplicates] (Box 94, Folder 92)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, March 24-May 7 (Box 95, Folder 93)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, April 20-May 22 (Box 95, Folder 94)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, February 2, March 24, April 20-30 (Box 95, Folder 95)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, May 1-22 (Box 95, Folder 96)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, May 17-June 5 (Box 95, Folder 97)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, May 28-June 11 (Box 95, Folder 98)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, May 23-June 16 (Box 95, Folder 99)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, May 23-June 16 (Box 95, Folder 100)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, May 23-June 16 [second duplicate] (Box 95, Folder 101)
  - G. Morris Carstairs notes, May 28 (Box 96, Folder 102)
  - Rorschach, 1-52 [two sets] (Box 96, Folder 103)
  - Rorschach, 1-52 [two sets] (Box 96, Folder 104)
  - TAT, 1-48 [two sets] (Box 96, Folder 105)
  - TAT, 1-48 [two sets] (Box 96, Folder 106)
  - TAT, re-presentations (Box 96, Folder 107)
  - Horn-Hellersberg [three sets] (Box 96, Folder 108)
  - Urban, Madras, Horn-Hellersberg (Box 96, Folder 109)
  - Unidentifed materials (Box 96, Folder 110)
  - Unidentifed materials (Box 96, Folder 111)